trade-it.co.uk 2008-06-18

# Online classifieds - Buy and sell classifieds - Classified advertising - Trade-It Classifieds in Bristol -

Trade-It is committed to protecting your right to privacy as a consumer of our online services.   
It is our policy to respect the privacy of private communication and the information you provide to us will be held on Trade-It computers that are based in the UK. 

We collect information about our users in order to help us continually improve the service we offer and so that we can enter into commercial arrangements, including the sale of advertising space, to provide more for our customers. Trade-It will always adhere to the UK Data Protection Legislation. 

This Privacy Policy only relates to the Trade-It service and does not extend to your use of the Internet outside of the Trade-It site. 

**What is a cookie?**   
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. 

Cookies record information about your online preferences. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalised services cannot then be provided to that user and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the advantage-ads.co.uk features. Each browser is different, so check the 'Help' menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

If you have set your computer to reject cookies you can still browse advantage-ads.co.uk anonymously until such time as you wish to register for Trade-It services. For further information on cookies please visit www.aboutcookies.org. 

**What data do we collect?**

We will collect personal data as provided to us during the registration process, which you agree to supply us as accurate. We will also collect personal data from other parts of the Trade-It site as required, for example, when customers enter competitions. We do not monitor your use of the Internet but we do use cookie technology to monitor your use of the Trade-It service. This information is not stored alongside your personal data and will only be used on an anonymous, aggregated basis. We may hold personal data relating to the transactions you enter into with Trade-It or others through Trade-It such as online retailers. We may also ask for other data so that we can obtain a better understanding of our users' requirements. This information will help us to sell appropriate advertising space and provide better personalisation services for our users. 

**What do we do with the data we collect?**   
We may use personal information about you to build up a profile of your interests and preferences. When you supply us with your details there will be a box to tick if you do not wish to receive email newsletters or other information which may be of interest to you. This information will not be disclosed to third parties. 

**Users aged 16 and under**   
If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parent/guardian's permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information on any Trade-It website. Users without this consent are not allowed to provide us with personal information. 

**Changing your contact details**   
You can update or amend your contact details at any time by using your My Account page which can be located on the Trade-It website. (Please note: You must be logged in to change your details) 

**Changes to the Policy**   
If we do change or amend our privacy policy we will notify users via the Trade-It website. The Privacy Policy will always be easily accessible online throughout all of the Trade-It services. 

Advertisement copy shall be legal, decent, honest and truthful; shall comply with the British Code of Advertising Practice and all other Codes under the general supervision of the Advertising Standards Authority: and shall comply with the requirements of current legislation.
